(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[♪ somber music playing]
[officer] Hold it right there!
[exclaims]
Don't touch me!
[crying]
[screams]
-[Takao] Tell me, Baudelaire...
-Don't touch me!
...are we really so sinful?
[crying]
You shit bug!
[Takao] Why do they confine us here?
[screams]
[Sawa screaming] Shit bug!
PREFECTURAL POLICE DEPARTMENT
[police] It's midnight.
What were you guys doing?
Your parents have filed
missing persons reports.
[Takao] We were merely scolded about
being out in the middle of the night.
They didn't ask about the gym clothes
or the classroom,
and Saeki, the victim of those incidents,
didn't say anything either.
-I...
-[♪ music fades]
We...
didn't get anywhere.
[♪ opening theme music playing]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 5
[boy 1] Don't push me in, guys.
Don't you dare! Whoa!
ONE MONTH LATER
[boy 2] Come on, that's not your size.
-It's so tight on you.
-It doesn't fit.
-[laughter]
-[indistinct chatter]
NO DIVING
[girl 1] We waited in the cold.
-[girl 2] You're unbelievable.
-[girl 3] Really.
[coach] Hey! [blows whistle]
No running!
-You're gonna trip!
-[students] Sorry, sir!
I got the new Young Magazine.
Wanna come over?
[chuckling] No way!
Should we invite anyone else?
Nah, don't bother. [chuckles]
[girls chattering indistinctly]
[Ai] Hey! Kasuga!
Who do you think you are?
Ai, it's okay.
It is not okay.
Nanako got lost
and her parents filed a report.
It was a serious situation!
They haven't found that creep yet, either!
But you don't even come talk to Nanako?
Are you even listening?
Saeki, I'm sure...
STYLE
::cue()
there's someone better for you than me.
What?
Right.
Got it.
[♪ somber music playing]
Thanks for everything.
Goodbye.
[Ai] You're the worst!
Nanako!
[♪ music fades]
[indistinct audio playing on TV]
Takao,
hurry up and eat.
[Takao] It seems...
I'm not really hungry today.
I sincerely apologize.
Please excuse me,
as I would like to go lie down in my room.
[Shizue sighs wearily]
We're summoning it?
[host] He claims
to be able to summon UFOs!
SUMMONING A UFO!?
[♪ eerie music playing]
[Takao] This town...
is already dead.
Flowers can do nothing but wait
to shrivel in the spot they bloomed in.
How about me?
It may seem like I can move about freely,
but, after all, I can't get anywhere.
I'll just shrivel up and die in this town.
[rain pattering]
[gasps]
[Takao] Nakamura!
[♪ music swells]
Don't rip any more holes...
in my soul!
Nakamura!
[growling]
[gasps]
[Takao] Of course.
That's it!
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Nakamura was hurting.
That's why she believed in someone
as empty as me.
And I just...
[grunts]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
[screaming]
Saeki is someone who can live a happy life
with or without me.
Nakamura, on the other hand...
I...
I won't leave Nakamura on her own!
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
-[class president] Stand up.
-[bell chimes]
-Bow.
-[teacher] See you tomorrow, everyone.
[students] See you tomorrow.
-[teacher] Go straight home.
-[students] Yes, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, Nanako,
where do you wanna go after school?
[Nanako] Let me think...
-Ready, set, one!
-[Ai] Hey.
Isn't Kasuga acting weird recently?
What? Who cares about him.
Ready, set, one!
-I win!
-That wasn't fair.
[Takao] Nakamura!
[panting] Nakamura!
I wrote this... last night.
Remember that promise we made?
Please read it.
Wait! I'll read it aloud, then,
so please listen!
"Nakamura, I'm sorry."
"I couldn't follow you to the other side."
"I hurt you."
"I'm a shit bug."
"But I'll work hard
and become a true pervert!"
"Nakamura, you won't be alone.
I'll make sure, because--"
-[exclaims]
-[man exclaims, yells]
Watch where you're going!
What school do you go to?!
Sorry, sir!
I'm sorry!
MASASHI IMAI
TOKI MINAMI
TAKAHASHI
NAKAMURA
[crows cawing]
Can I help you?
No. Well... Uh...
I mean...
I'm Kasuga.
I see.
You know, when Nakamura...
I mean, when Sawa was...
We were in the mountains and...
I'm very sorry about what I did.
Tell me the rest inside.
NAKAMURA
[Takao] Thank you, sir.
[Kazuyuki] Sawa ain't home yet.
[can hisses]
Ah.
So, what kind of friend are you to Sawa?
What kind...
She's a real handful.
Doesn't listen to what I say,
has a bad mouth,
and doesn't come home at all.
I wonder who on earth she takes after.
[♪ slow instrumental music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
You see,
I got divorced when Sawa was five,
so she grew up without a mother.
This is the first time
a friend has visited.
The thing is...
I don't know.
I don't know if we're friends.
And I don't know...
what's going on inside her head.
But, I...
I want to know.
Why don'tcha stay for supper?
[Takao] Thank you, but...
Could I use your restroom, please?
Sure, it's down there.
[♪ music fades]
[crows cawing]
STAY OUT SHIT BUG
[Takao] It smells like...
Nakamura.
Hmm?
PERVERT
SO DUMB. EVERYBODY IS.
THERE ARE ONLY SHIT BUGS...
I CAN'T STAND IT.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Sawa] So dumb.
Everybody is.
Scum. Scum. Scum. Boring.
It's so boring.
There are only shit bugs in this town.
I can't stand it.
Everything's rusted and filthy.
I am a pervert.
I am a pervert. I am a pervert.
It's dumb. Everyone's scum.
I found someone!
Takao Kasuga. He's a pervert.
I should make a contract with him!
I want you...
to make a contract with me.
[Takao] A contract?
[Sawa] I made Kasuga
put on Nanako Saeki's gym clothes.
He seemed happy.
He's a pervert, just as I thought.
Kasuga had the nerve
to start dating Nanako Saeki.
How dare he. I'll peel all his layers.
We turned the classroom
into a sea of shit bugs.
It felt great.
I knew I saw something in him.
With Kasuga, I'm sure I can go...
to the other side!
We couldn't go to the other side.
WE COULDN'T GO TO THE OTHER SIDE.
WE COULDN'T GO.
We couldn't go.
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[Takao gasps softly]
Nakamura...
[screams]
Get out, you turd!
Nakamura!
[panting] Wait!
Please wait!
[grunting, exclaims]
-[groans]
-[Takao panting] Nakamura!
Please...
I want to find the other side...
In this town. With you.
[screaming]
Who do you think you are?
You scum! You worthless scum!
What other side, you pile of mud!
Spend the rest of your life
fondling it yourself, you scum!
Nakamura...
Make a contract with me, one more time.
This time,
let's vow to crawl out
of this sea of shit bugs.
I swear...
I'll show you the other side
without leaving this town.
[♪ soft music playing]
DANGEROUS - DO NOT ENTER!
[Ai] Nanako.
[chuckles] What class do we have next?
STYLE
::cue()
[grunting]
[exhales]
[both] Rock, paper, scissors!
[loud chatter]
[laughing] Then, out of nowhere,
my mom walked in.
[laughs] You're an idiot.
[Kojima and Yamada laughing]
[laughing] Yeah. Been there, done that.
What the heck?
Why are you being all weird?
What? Come on, I'm always like this.
[chuckling]
[Yamada] Huh...
[Takao chuckles nervously]
Tomorrow,
come to the riverbank
beyond the floodgate.
It'll be complete, tomorrow.
[crows cawing in distance]
[man on TV] In order to summon the
flying object emitting peculiar lights,
our experts...
That's right. I got this for you, Takao.
How much do you think it was?
I don't need...
books anymore.
Oh.
[chuckles] This is delicious!
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Takao] That's right.
I don't need books anymore.
[whistle blows]
[Takao] They've given up
on feeling emotions,
but will they belittle me as "a pervert"?
Trapped with those numb bastards...
left to rot, with nowhere to go...
I won't let that happen to me.
[laughter]
[Takao] I'm going to do this.
A place that will make Nakamura laugh.
That's going to be...
GIRLS' CHANGING ROOM
"the other side" for me.
[♪ music fades]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
You guys, my panties are gone.
[girls exclaiming]
[Ai] What? No way.
[girl] Mine are gone, too.
[girls chattering, exclaiming]
Are yours missing, too, Nanako?
What? Yeah.
-[Ai] I wonder who did it.
-[Nanako] Right?
[excited chatter]
STYLE
::cue()
I've been waiting.
Nakamura.
This space...
Just this space
will be "the other side" within this town.
Come here whenever you want.
Even if we can't get out of this town,
I'll make sure you're never bored.
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
You just sit here, Nakamura.
That's the contract...
I'll make with you.
You're talking
like you've got it all figured out...
You've got some nerve to steal mine, too.
The only one you didn't take
was Nanako Saeki's.
Why?
Because...
that's the worst thing I could do.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm letting you make a contract with me,
you absolute pervert.
Do I make myself clear?
Yeah!
[♪ music fades]
[Ai] Nanako!
[Nanako sobbing]
Ai... Sorry for calling all of a sudden.
It's just...
I'm a weak human being.
[♪ closing theme music playing]
I can't... [sniffles]
carry it all on my own, anymore...
TO BE CONTINUED
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
[narrator] Kasuga and Nakamura
make a secret plan,
and jealousy bursts into bloom
in Saeki's heart as she finds out.
Next, on episode six,
Saeki's madness burns
all of Kasuga's hopes to the ground.
Translated by Yuka Kristi